{
  "homeworks": [
    {
      "__class": "Homework",
      "id": "5d0fb2f7-4fa5-4e62-828b-f61f84c6f030",
      "name": "Homework 2021/04/14",
      "status": "active",
      "tasks": [
        {
          "id": "a5f52bf9-f0d2-49e0-aa0a-a5d556e7a441",
          "type": "none",
          "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
          "correctAnswer": 4,
          "problem": "2 + 2",
          "__ver": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": "77a85a4b-5c04-46dd-a919-431c04aec682",
          "type": "none",
          "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
          "correctAnswer": 5,
          "problem": "4 + 1",
          "__ver": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": "7e27ae40-bc61-41d5-80ba-a82265e2c74d",
          "type": "none",
          "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
          "correctAnswer": 8,
          "problem": "5 + 3",
          "__ver": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": "cf8a13d4-3450-49b4-96fa-5270c0f3ebde",
          "type": "none",
          "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
          "correctAnswer": 7,
          "problem": "2 + 5",
          "__ver": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": "6d09c86a-8335-4a28-ad56-f1266fc2e26b",
          "type": "none",
          "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
          "correctAnswer": 8,
          "problem": "0 + 8",
          "__ver": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": "ed055862-3f1b-4201-a726-478747da0f83",
          "type": "none",
          "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
          "correctAnswer": 4,
          "problem": "5 - 1",
          "__ver": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": "b8bf613b-4beb-4511-9a67-53a73066a13f",
          "type": "none",
          "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
          "correctAnswer": 2,
          "problem": "5 - 3",
          "__ver": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": "44b6e0a7-57ec-40b5-ae6a-aaca60114ad8",
          "type": "none",
          "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
          "correctAnswer": 12,
          "problem": "2 + 10",
          "__ver": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": "d119db89-0c67-4aba-a0bd-b13516c4178c",
          "type": "none",
          "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
          "correctAnswer": 12,
          "problem": "11 + 1",
          "__ver": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": "0ffdfcf0-0e85-4a78-9d71-680c9dfb6e1c",
          "type": "none",
          "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
          "correctAnswer": 13,
          "problem": "4 + 9",
          "__ver": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": "f0a4e193-7d51-48a0-a686-fc99ca02a80c",
          "type": "none",
          "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
          "correctAnswer": 18,
          "problem": "6 + 12",
          "__ver": "1"
        }
      ],
      "__ver": "1"
    }
  ],
  "tasks": [
    {
      "id": "77a85a4b-5c04-46dd-a919-431c04aec682",
      "solved": true,
      "state": {
        "answer": "5"
      },
      "__ver": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": "a5f52bf9-f0d2-49e0-aa0a-a5d556e7a441",
      "solved": true,
      "state": {
        "answer": "4"
      },
      "__ver": "1"
    }
  ],
  "logs": [
    {
      "timestamp": 1618882770490,
      "type": "task-answer",
      "msg": "2 + 2 = 3",
      "target": "a5f52bf9-f0d2-49e0-aa0a-a5d556e7a441",
      "data": {
        "problem": "2 + 2",
        "answer": "3",
        "expected": 4,
        "correct": false,
        "attemptTime": 0
      },
      "id": 1,
      "__ver": "1"
    },
    {
      "timestamp": 1618882772219,
      "type": "task-answer",
      "msg": "2 + 2 = 3",
      "target": "a5f52bf9-f0d2-49e0-aa0a-a5d556e7a441",
      "data": {
        "problem": "2 + 2",
        "answer": "3",
        "expected": 4,
        "correct": false,
        "attemptTime": 1729
      },
      "id": 2,
      "__ver": "1"
    },
    {
      "timestamp": 1618882772612,
      "type": "task-answer",
      "msg": "2 + 2 = 3",
      "target": "a5f52bf9-f0d2-49e0-aa0a-a5d556e7a441",
      "data": {
        "problem": "2 + 2",
        "answer": "3",
        "expected": 4,
        "correct": false,
        "attemptTime": 393
      },
      "id": 3,
      "__ver": "1"
    },
    {
      "timestamp": 1618882774573,
      "type": "task-answer",
      "msg": "2 + 2 = 2",
      "target": "a5f52bf9-f0d2-49e0-aa0a-a5d556e7a441",
      "data": {
        "problem": "2 + 2",
        "answer": "2",
        "expected": 4,
        "correct": false,
        "attemptTime": 1961
      },
      "id": 4,
      "__ver": "1"
    },
    {
      "timestamp": 1618882776699,
      "type": "task-answer",
      "msg": "2 + 2 = 4",
      "target": "a5f52bf9-f0d2-49e0-aa0a-a5d556e7a441",
      "data": {
        "problem": "2 + 2",
        "answer": "4",
        "expected": 4,
        "correct": true,
        "attemptTime": 7854
      },
      "id": 5,
      "__ver": "1"
    },
    {
      "timestamp": 1618882778916,
      "type": "task-answer",
      "msg": "4 + 1 = ?",
      "target": "77a85a4b-5c04-46dd-a919-431c04aec682",
      "data": {
        "problem": "4 + 1",
        "expected": 5,
        "correct": false,
        "attemptTime": 2217
      },
      "id": 6,
      "__ver": "1"
    },
    {
      "timestamp": 1618882780253,
      "type": "task-answer",
      "msg": "4 + 1 = 2",
      "target": "77a85a4b-5c04-46dd-a919-431c04aec682",
      "data": {
        "problem": "4 + 1",
        "answer": "2",
        "expected": 5,
        "correct": false,
        "attemptTime": 1337
      },
      "id": 7,
      "__ver": "1"
    },
    {
      "timestamp": 1618882782056,
      "type": "task-answer",
      "msg": "4 + 1 = 23",
      "target": "77a85a4b-5c04-46dd-a919-431c04aec682",
      "data": {
        "problem": "4 + 1",
        "answer": "23",
        "expected": 5,
        "correct": false,
        "attemptTime": 1803
      },
      "id": 8,
      "__ver": "1"
    },
    {
      "timestamp": 1618882783733,
      "type": "task-answer",
      "msg": "4 + 1 = 5",
      "target": "77a85a4b-5c04-46dd-a919-431c04aec682",
      "data": {
        "problem": "4 + 1",
        "answer": "5",
        "expected": 5,
        "correct": true,
        "attemptTime": 6029
      },
      "id": 9,
      "__ver": "1"
    }
  ]
}